{"VIDEO_ID":"8W4WKsyuGUY","MODEL_SIZE":"tiny","COMPUTE_TYPE":"float32","VERSIONS":{"ctranslate2":"3.15.1","faster_whisper":"0.6.0","yt-dlp":"2023.3.4","onnxruntime":"1.15.0"},"TranscriptionOptions":{"beam_size":1,"best_of":5,"patience":1,"length_penalty":1,"log_prob_threshold":-1.0,"no_speech_threshold":0.6,"compression_ratio_threshold":2.4,"condition_on_previous_text":true,"temperatures":[0.0,0.2,0.4,0.6,0.8,1.0],"initial_prompt":null,"prefix":null,"suppress_blank":true,"suppress_tokens":[-1],"without_timestamps":false,"max_initial_timestamp":1.0,"word_timestamps":false,"prepend_punctuations":"\"'\u201c\u00bf([\u3001"},"VadOptions":{"threshold":0.5,"min_speech_duration_ms":250,"max_speech_duration_s":Infinity,"min_silence_duration_ms":2000,"window_size_samples":1024,"speech_pad_ms":400}}
DISCLAIMER: Subtitles are machine generated.
There is no guarantee that the translation is accurate or correct.
Guys is gone...
If you areiks, leave the comments below...
If I'm crazy...
Comments...
If you are now sleeping on that ski
What was that stupid F楽 chant?
At the beginning of the gym, I got that impression,
but when I arrived in the gym, I realized I was getting a lot afters...
That was once to get a lot of心...
eh...
I'm a little nervous.
I'm a little nervous…
Please say hello to my friends.
I'm a little nervous.
Thank you for watching!