{"VIDEO_ID":"8W4WKsyuGUY","MODEL_SIZE":"tiny","COMPUTE_TYPE":"int8","VERSIONS":{"ctranslate2":"3.15.1","faster_whisper":"0.6.0","yt-dlp":"2023.3.4","onnxruntime":"1.15.0"},"TranscriptionOptions":{"beam_size":1,"best_of":5,"patience":1,"length_penalty":1,"log_prob_threshold":-1.0,"no_speech_threshold":0.6,"compression_ratio_threshold":2.4,"condition_on_previous_text":true,"temperatures":[0.0,0.2,0.4,0.6,0.8,1.0],"initial_prompt":null,"prefix":null,"suppress_blank":true,"suppress_tokens":[-1],"without_timestamps":false,"max_initial_timestamp":1.0,"word_timestamps":false,"prepend_punctuations":"\"'\u201c\u00bf([\u3001"},"VadOptions":{"threshold":0.5,"min_speech_duration_ms":250,"max_speech_duration_s":Infinity,"min_silence_duration_ms":2000,"window_size_samples":1024,"speech_pad_ms":400}}
DISCLAIMER: Subtitles are machine generated.
There is no guarantee that the translation is accurate or correct.
I'm scared.
Chicken clienton Art squats.
I'm shouting at him in the middle of the street when my mom's battle is high.
I can't change myativa, while I was eating chicken aого glasses.
I can't get there.
I can't.
I can't!
I can't stand it.
I'm hoping to lose you,
it's tough, but it's just
actually a very hard ninety or a ninety
Yay!
This is a girl from the pile boom.
I guess, it's done!
Let's move on to…
seeds!
Let's have different colors,
which aren't as good asI thought.
Get your累了!